Hi, I'm Benedict Cumberbatch and I'm here at BuzzFeed
嗨，我是本尼迪克特·康伯巴奇，我在BuzzFeed
and I'm here to play with puppies
我在这里和小狗一起玩
and to answer your questions
并且回答您的问题
I'm excited, I'm excited to meet the pups
我很兴奋，见到幼崽我很高兴
Bring in the pups
把小狗带来
Hello, you're a big puppy
你好，你是一只大狗
What are we doing in here?
我们在这里干什么？
What a strange environment to be in
多奇怪的环境啊
What was that noise?
那是什么声音？
What's in the jar, what's in the jar, what's in the jar?
罐子里有什么，罐子里有什么，罐子里有什么？
What's this, what's this?
这是什么这是什么？
What's this, it's a question
这是什么，这是个问题
关于扮演奇异博士最棒和最糟糕的事分别是什么？
The best thing is, yeah, you eat that question
最棒的事是，你咬了那张纸条
eat it up, yeah, yeah
咬断了，好吧，好吧
There's a lot of best things about it
关于它有很多最棒的事情
The best thing is probably having
最棒的事情可能是
a cloak that means I can fly
拥有一件披风意味着我可以飞翔
which means I get to do wire work
这意味着我要吊着威亚来工作了
which, when it's done right, and not for too long
如果做得对，而且时间不长
in a harness is incredibly good fun
戴上威亚是一件很有趣的事
some of the stunts are really good fun to do
有些特技真的很有趣
The training and all of that, I really enjoy
训练和所有的这些，我真的很喜欢
It's a big old work out
这是一项规模很大的工作
Yes, it is!
是的！
The worst thing is, I don't know
最糟糕的事是，我不知道
it's a really gifted gig, I'm very lucky
这是一次非常有天赋的演出，我很幸运
If I had to moan about something, what would it be?
如果我不得不抱怨什么，那会是什么？
Maybe the cloak, again, the cloak is quite cumbersome
也许是披风，再一次强调，披风相当笨重
No pun intended, hello
没有双关语，你好
Yeah, it can be quite a sort of awkward thing to work with
是的，这可能有点尴尬
Cookie jar, no, I'm joking, it's questions, I'm so sorry
曲奇罐，不，我在开玩笑，这是问题，很抱歉
你还会拉小提琴吗？ 如果是的话，你最喜欢演奏什么歌？
do I still know?
我还知道吗？
I never knew how to play the violin, next question
我从来不知道怎么拉小提琴，下一个问题
It was all fakery and really embarrassing
这都是假的，真的很尴尬
You know, this is something that takes years of practices
你知道，这需要多年的实践
from the age of three and then I'm supposed to
从三岁起我就应该这么练习
sort of turn it around in a couple of months
或许几个月后就会好转
before doing a bit of Sherlock
在表演夏洛克之前
Not good, my friends
感觉真糟，我的朋友们
I can pretend to be a lot of things
我可以假装会很多东西
with some degree of authenticity
让它具有一定程度的真实性
but that is something well beyond me
但这远远超出了我的能力范围
如果有《夏洛克》的第五季，你会想要和你所扮演的角色发生点什么吗？
Next question
下一个问题
“谁是你在好莱坞结交的第一个真正的朋友？ 你们两个还有联系吗？”
I don't know, I mean, Gary Oldman, I guess?
我不知道，我是说，加里·奥德曼，我猜？
Yeah, we still speak
是的，我们还有联系
First time I went to Hollywood, I did "Star Trek"
我第一次去好莱坞时，我出演了《星际迷航》
and I don't speak to them nearly
我几乎不和他们说话
I mean, I see more of, obviously
我的意思是，很明显，我看到了更多
because of the Marvel thing
因为漫威的事
but Chris, I adore, and,
但是克里斯，我很崇拜他，
you know, and Zachary as well.
你知道，还有扎卡里
Yeah, it is a great family
是的，这是一个很棒的家庭
It was a great family to be a part of for a little while there
在那里呆了一段时间，那是一个伟大的家庭
And darling Anton, as well
还有亲爱的安东
who I wish I could still speak to, very sad
我希望我仍然可以和他联系，这非常令人难过
Don't eat my questions before I've read them
在我读这些问题之前，请不要咬它们
It's like having naked flames in the room
就像房间里有明火
this is wonderful
这太棒了
在扮演了帕特里克·梅尔罗斯这样的角色后，要重新回到正常生活有多难？
Good question
好问题
Difficult, I abstracted myself from my normal life
很难，我把自己从正常生活中抽离出来
for a little while, especially when I went to the dark zone
有一段时间，特别是当我去了黑暗的地方时
of cocaine and heroin abuse and trashing hotel rooms
滥用可卡因和海洛因并捣毁旅客客房
in the New York episode
在纽约的情节中
Just didn't really want to go home
只是真的不想回家
with any of that swirling around my brain and body
任何围绕在我的大脑和身体旋转的东西
I mean, not literally, but just psychically
我的意思是，不是字面上的，而是心理上的
and unphysically, because you just have to pretend
它不是生理上，因为你只需要假装
and put yourself there and you need some space
把自己放在那里，你需要一些空间
But most of the time, I switch on and off pretty easily
但大多数时候，我很容易将自己抽离和沉浸其中
你手机上哪个应用程序用得最多？
Probably Waze
可能是位智地图
Hey, go easy, you may be bigger
嘿，走开，你也许是要大上一点
but that's not playing fair, stop it, stop it.
但这不公平，住手，住手
yeah, pick on someone your own size
是的，选一个和你自己体型差不多的小狗
No, no, no, no
不，不，不，不
no, no, no, no
如果你能对你小时候喜欢的任何电视节目进行电影改编，会是哪一个？
Why would I want to do a film of
我为什么要拍电影
something that worked well in its time as a TV series?
在一个电视连续剧大热的时代？
I mean, don't get me wrong, I get that happens a lot
我是说，别误会，我知道这事经常发生
but that's not really, that's not my gig
但那不是真的，那不是我的演出
I'm not too fond of that stuff
我不太喜欢那些东西
你是否打算加入Instagram或Twitter？
Did not, no, absolutely not.
没有，没有，绝对没有。
谁是您一直以来最喜欢的歌手？
你现在正在听哪些当代艺术家的作品？
I don't have all-time favorite
我没有一直喜欢的音乐家
I mean, Bowie, the Stones, the Ramones
我是说，大卫鲍威，滚石乐队，雷蒙斯乐队
Sex Pistols, Clash, Who, Pink Floyd
性手枪，碰撞乐队，谁人乐队，平克·弗洛伊德
What am I listening to at the moment?
我现在在听什么？
Well, there's a new album, it's great
嗯，有一张新专辑，很棒
A Moon Shaped Pool gets a lot of play, Radiohead
《月形池》里有很多不错的，来自电台司令乐队的专辑(2016年)
I love Tom's new album as well
我也喜欢汤姆的新专辑
it's a very good film he did with Paul Thomas Anderson
这是他和保罗·托马斯·安德森合作拍摄的一部很好的电影
I am being so serious whilst your relative chews my boot
当你的亲近我咬住我的靴子的时候，我却是如此严肃
You want to chew my boot?
你想咬我的靴子吗？
描述完美的一天
hello
嗨
This is a perfect day, isn't it?
今天真是完美的一天，不是吗？
Getting my ear licked by a puppy
我的耳朵被小狗舔了
Yeah, this is pretty perfect, this is great
是啊，太完美了，这很棒
but I mean, the rest of perfect with me would be private
但我的意思是，其余的完美将是我私有的
so I won't describe that
所以我不会描述这个
Work-wise, though, a perfect day is
然而，明智的做法应该是，完美的一天是
I don't know, I love my job
我不知道，我喜欢我的工作
pretty much every day is a good one
每天几乎都是美好的一天
A perfect day is when I've had eight hours sleep
最完美的一天是我拥有了八个小时的睡眠
That's a perfect day
那是完美的一天
你最不能忍受的是什么？
oh, god, but people sound so grouchy
哦，上帝，但人们听起来很不高兴
when they answer these questions, I don't know
当他们回答这些问题时，我不知道
People leaning on the horn
人们按响喇叭
thinking it's gonna make traffic move faster
以为会让交通更快
People being trapped in their bubble, you know
人们被困在信息泡沫中，你明白吗
People being trapped in their bubble full stop
被困在泡沫中的人们将停止思考
Mobile phone usage
手机使用情况
Negative impact of some of social media
一些社交媒体的负面影响
I mean, I could go on
我是说，我可以继续
I'm an old fogy now, 43, sufficient
我现在是个老赶不上时代的人了，已经43岁了，够了
Good question, I really could go on
好问题，我真的可以继续下去
So I will
所以我会
Dirty tricks, demagoguery
肮脏的把戏，蛊惑人心的罪恶
fake news, everyone's a critic and angry but
假新闻，每个人都是有批判性的愤世嫉俗的
they don't necessarily have any kind of nuance
但他们不一定有任何细微的差别
they just want to shoot the messenger sometimes
他们有时只想开枪
and not the message
而不是传递信息
The fact that we're in a crisis people
我们现在处于危机之中
a climate crisis, these little puppy dogs
气候危机，这些小狗
Save the puppies if not yourselves
如果不是你们自己的话，请保护这些小狗
Stop using single-use plastic
停止使用一次性塑料
Try and stop digging carbon fuels out of the ground
试着停止从地下挖掘碳燃料
Please, leave the fossil fuels alone for these puppies
请把化石燃料留给这些小狗吧
That's dangerous question to give me
这个给我的问题很危险啊
Yeah, can I have another pet peeve
是啊，我能再继续抱怨吗
yeah, burning rainforests
还有，燃烧的雨林
what the (bleeps) is wrong with the world?
这个世界出了什么问题？
在你的漫威电影巡回宣传期间，照顾汤姆·霍兰德是什么感觉？
Difficult, like I said, I had to teach the kid how to shave,
很难，就像我说的那样，我得教孩子刮胡子
how to brush his teeth, the fact that he had to do it
如何刷牙，他不得不这样做的原因
both day and night
无论白天还是黑夜
you know, personal hygiene's
你知道，个人卫生
a bit of an issue with teenagers
青少年有的问题
and Tom's no exception to that rule
汤姆也不例外
So, you know, I'd get the rooms
所以，你知道，我要回到房间
I'd get out the, it was tricky
我要出去，这很棘手
But, you know, he's in all honesty
但是，老实说，你知道的他很诚实
he's a gentlemen, brilliant, wise beyond his years
他是个绅士，才华横溢，有着超越年龄的智慧
A dear friend, I love working with him
亲爱的朋友，我喜欢和他一起工作
and bring on the next project, goodbye
并进行下一个演出，再见
Thanks so much
非常感谢
I'm Benedict Cumberbatch, watch my movie
我是本尼迪克特·康伯巴奇，看我的电影
it's called "The Current War"
它被称为“电力之战”
it's not mine, it belongs to other people, too
这不是我的，它也属于其他人
it's really good
真的很好
North Shore Animal League America
美国北岸动物联盟
thank you puppies, and thank you for looking after them
谢谢你的小狗，谢谢你照顾他们
they're very sweet
他们很可爱
byebye
再见